<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Lifestyle &#8211; Invisere</title>
	<atom:link href="http://invisere.tech/category/lifestyle/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://invisere.tech</link>
	<description>Ja saps on vols anar?</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 12:59:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>ca</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Grass and Tree Covered Village Luzern</title>
		<link>http://invisere.tech/2020/12/16/grass-and-tree-covered-village-luzern/</link>
					<comments>http://invisere.tech/2020/12/16/grass-and-tree-covered-village-luzern/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 15:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CSS3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HTML5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UX / UI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.athenadesignstudio.com/themes/sena-wp/?p=108</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Quisque dui at erat auctor pulvinar nisl felis, gravida et aliquam vitae, aliquet quis nibh. Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium. But I must explain to you how all this mistaken idea of denouncing pleasure and praising pain was born and I will give you a complete account [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>
Quisque dui at erat auctor pulvinar nisl felis, gravida et aliquam vitae, aliquet quis nibh.
										

</p>



<span id="more-108"></span>



<p>Sed ut perspiciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laudantium.</p>



<p>But I must explain to you how all this mistaken idea of denouncing pleasure and praising pain was born and <strong>I will give you a complete account of the system</strong>, and expound the actual teachings of the great explorer of the truth, the master-builder of human happiness.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Ignissimos ducimus qui blanditiis praesentium volup tatum deleniti atque corrupti quos dolores.</p><cite>Diana Bowman</cite></blockquote>



<p><strong>No one rejects, dislikes, or avoids pleasure itself</strong>, because it is pleasure, but because those who do not know how to pursue pleasure rationally encounter consequences that are extremely painful.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery columns-2 is-cropped image-slider"><ul class="blocks-gallery-grid"><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img src="http://www.athenadesignstudio.com/themes/sena-wp/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/post-slide-1-1024x512.jpg" alt="" data-id="104" data-full-url="http://invisere.tech/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/post-slide-1.jpg" data-link="http://www.athenadesignstudio.com/themes/sena-wp/?attachment_id=104" class="wp-image-104"/></figure></li><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img src="http://www.athenadesignstudio.com/themes/sena-wp/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/post-slide-2-1024x512.jpg" alt="" data-id="105" data-full-url="http://invisere.tech/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/post-slide-2.jpg" data-link="http://www.athenadesignstudio.com/themes/sena-wp/?attachment_id=105" class="wp-image-105"/></figure></li></ul></figure>



<p>Nor again is there anyone who loves or pursues or desires to obtain pain of  itself, because it is pain, but because occasionally circumstances  occur in which toil and pain can procure him some great pleasure.</p>



<p>But in certain circumstances and owing to the claims of duty or the obligations of business it will frequently occur that <strong>pleasures have to be repudiated and annoyances accepted</strong>. The wise man therefore always holds in these matters to this principle of selection: he rejects pleasures to secure other greater pleasures, or else he endures pains to avoid worse pains.</p>



<p>I feel the presence of the Almighty:</p>



<ol><li><strong>Impenetrable foliage</strong> of my trees, and but a few stray gleams.</li><li><strong>A wonderful serenity</strong> has taken possession of my entire soul.</li><li><strong>I should be incapable of drawing</strong> a single stroke at the present moment.</li></ol>



<p>I am so happy, my dear friend, so absorbed in the exquisite sense of  mere tranquil existence, that I neglect my talents. I should be  incapable of drawing a single stroke at the present moment and yet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube clearfix wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<div class="embed-container"><iframe loading="lazy" title="5 BEGINNER PHOTOGRAPHY MISTAKES + How to Solve Them!" width="750" height="422" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3YWH1ZJwRsE?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe></div>
</div></figure>



<p>One morning, when Gregor Samsa woke from troubled dreams, he found  himself transformed in his bed into a horrible vermin. He lay on his  armour-like back, and if he lifted his head a little he could see his  brown belly, slightly domed and divided by arches into stiff sections.  The bedding was hardly able to cover it and seemed ready to slide off  any moment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://invisere.tech/2020/12/16/grass-and-tree-covered-village-luzern/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
